<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mike Ornstein</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mike Ornstein</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Template Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/template/</guid>
      <description>My Blog Post Here is an introductory paragraph with some bold text and some italic text.
Heading 1 Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Heading 6 Standard Formatting This is strikethrough text.
This is italic text. This is italic text.
This is bold text. This is bold text.
Lists Unordered Item 1 Item 2 Subitem 1 Subitem 2 Item 3 Ordered First item Second item Subitem 1 Subitem 2 Third item Quotes Here is a block quote:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roof Shade - Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/house-projects/roof-shade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/house-projects/roof-shade/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview A lot of work into these roof shades&amp;hellip; this is a many part series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto Roller Shade</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/house-projects/auto-roller-shades/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/house-projects/auto-roller-shades/</guid>
      <description>We like to open and close the shades more now that we can ask Alexa to do it.
THE END RESULT
PARTS LIST
Key bits that makes this work:
The motor with a radio - Somfy Roll Up Wirefree R28 RTS Motor The motor radio to z-wave thing - Somfy ZRTSI RTS 16 Channel Z-Wave to RTS Plug-in Interface Wall Module Wink Hub - The z-wave thing to internet thing An Alexa Device - Echo Dot IFTTT There are also some other little bits that are needed, but are less exciting:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drivetrain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/drivetrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/drivetrain/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview race car project for credit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uprights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/uprights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/uprights/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview This was a project for race car team. I designed, analyzed, and fabricated the uprights for the car.
Project Goal </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMR 57 Body</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/formula-sae/body/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Trials and tribulations of sketch to finished carbon car body for Carnegie Mellon Racing&amp;rsquo;s #57 car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Bot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/monkeybot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/monkeybot/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview A robot that was supposed to be able to swing dynamically from monkey bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibratron</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/vibratron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/vibratron/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Built out of a Vibraphone, Vibratron played was a robotic instrument that used recirculating ball bearings to hit keys on a circularly re-constructed vibraphone. This instrument was part of the Robotics club RobOrchestra.
Team Members Andrew Burks!
Contributions Aesthetic Design The distributor The lift </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyLo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/hylo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/hylo/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview A robot that has legs and wheels! Hybrid Locomotion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Arm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/humanoid-lab/soft-arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/humanoid-lab/soft-arm/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview The Humanoids Lab and the Quality of Life Technologies group and Carnegie Mellon formed a project whose goal was to create an inherently safe robot that was able to do useful work.
This work was presented at the EBMC 2011 conference with the paper, Physical Human Interaction for an Inflatable Manipulator
It also turned out to be the inspiration for Baymax of Big Hero 6! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Wrist and Gripper</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/humanoid-lab/soft-wrist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/humanoid-lab/soft-wrist/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview A wrist actuated by tendons to move around an inflatable grasper. Provisionally patented! </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/mobot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/roboclub/mobot/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Mobot is an annual activity at CMU. As a freshman, I wanted to enter into the competition, so joined forces with some savvy electronics and software folks to put together a car. I put the chassis of the beast together and did all the integration with wheels, sensors and compute. We didn&amp;rsquo;t do too well, but it was a fun start to robot building in Robotics Club!
Team Members Jitu Das Harrison Rose Project Goal develop a robot using parts literally off the shelf (megashelf!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
